Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 1, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Banking, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: American Bankers Association
    Notes: Sept.
- Box: 1, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Cyanamid Suggestion Plan Manual for Supervisors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Author: American Cyanamid Co. Communications Suggestion Systems
- Box: 1, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Author: American District Telegraph Co.
    Notes: Jan. 1, 1949
- Box: 1, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Protection, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Author: American Dyeing Corp.
    Notes: Nov. 1, 1955
- Box: 1, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Author: American Fore Loyalty Group
- Box: 1, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Protection for You and Your Family, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Author: American Gas and Electric Corp.
    Notes: Feb. 24
  - Item 2: Protectin for Employees and Their Families, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Author: American Gas and Electric Corp
    Notes: April 4, 1958
- Box: 1, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plans:A Personnel Relations Program, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Author: American Hospital Association
- Box: 1, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Corn Ear, 1074; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: American Maize-Products Company
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 4 Nov.-Dec.
- Box: 1, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: American Metal Climax, Inc.
    Notes: 1/1/65
  - Item 2: Group Life Insurance Program for Salaried Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 3. 1965
  - Item 3: Supplemental Life Insurance Program for Salaried Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 3, 1965
  - Item 4: Salaried Employees Personal Accident Insurance, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: Sept. 2, 1965
  - Item 5: Basic Hospital Surgical Medical Expense Protection, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Service Benefit Area, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Salaried Employee's Benefit Plans, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: Stock Purchase Thrift Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Hospital Surgical Medical Expense and Medical Expenses and Reimbursemnt Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: Supplemental Pension and Profit Sharing Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 11: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees at Climax and Empire, Colorado, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 12: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees (except at Climax and Empire, Colorado), 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 13: Medical Expenses Reimbursement Plan for Salaried Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: Aug. 6, 1964
- Box: 1, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Publications List, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: American Nurses' Association
  - Item 2: Report of the Committee on Economic and General Welfare, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: Jan. 29, 1959
  - Item 3: An ANA Retirement Plan for Nurses, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Box: 1, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Non-Contributory Pension Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Author: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp. and Participating Subsidiary Companies
    Notes: April 1, 1950
  - Item 2: Insurance Program, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Author: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corp.
  - Item 3: Planning for the Years of Retirement, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: A Plan of Group Insurance for Hourly Paid Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: July 1, 1950
  - Item 5: Non-Contributory Pension Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: Aug. 1, 1950
  - Item 7: Annual Reports, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 8: Planning for the Years of Retirement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Box: 1, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Author: American Seating Company
  - Item 2: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Your Pension Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: Jan. 1,1951
- Box: 1, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: News, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Author: American Smelting and Refining Company
    Notes: Fall Vol. 14, No. 3
- Box: 1, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Association Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Author: American Society for Personnel Administration
    Notes: Feb.
  - Item 2: Association Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Action, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 3 June
  - Item 4: Washington Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: Association Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 6: Associatino Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Box: 1, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Human Behavior in Employee-Employer Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Author: John A. Patton
    Notes: June 16, 1947
- Box: 1, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Job Description Recommended Procedure, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Author: American Steel Foundries
    Notes: Jan. 10, 1947
  - Item 2: How to Improve, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Box: 1, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Purposeful Travel, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: American Travel Association
    Notes: Oct. Issue 10
  - Item 2: Purposeful Travel, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Dec. Issue 9
  - Item 3: Travel in 68', 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Pension and wlefare News, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Sept. Vol. 1, No. 12
  - Item 5: Purposeful Travel, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: March Issue 7
  - Item 6: Travel 1965, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: Don Dougherty
  - Item 7: Israel/Italy, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 8: Mexico, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 9: Purposeful Travel, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Nov. Issue 6
  - Item 10: Purposeful Travel, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Aug. Issue 5
  - Item 11: ATA Travel Notes, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Feb. 13 1961
  - Item 12: ATA Travel Notes, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 13: ATA Travel Notes, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: March 1, 1963
  - Item 14: Purposeful Travel, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Sept. Issue 2
  - Item 15: Travel Notes from American Travel Association, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 16: Royal Caribbean Air/Sea Cruise, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 17: Purposeful Travel, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Dec. Issue 3
  - Item 18: Journey Toward Understanding, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 19: Come to New York Visit United Nations See World Fair, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 20: Purposeful Travel, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: April Issue 4
  - Item 21: Caribbean, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Fall-Winter
  - Item 22: Queen Mary and Queen Elizabeth Bermuda and Nassau Cruises, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 23: Purposeful Travel, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Aug. Issue 7
  - Item 24: Two Caribbean Holidays Dominican Republic and Haiti, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 25: Travel in 67', 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 26: Letter, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Notes: Jan
- Box: 1, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: ATF Pension Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Author: American Type Founders, Inc.
- Box: 1, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Box: 1, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Partners in Velvet, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: Clarence A. Wimpfheimer
    Notes: Reprinted from The Textile Engineer Summer
  - Item 2: Profit sharing Really Works at American Velvet Co., 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: E.H. Helliwell
    Notes: Reprinted from Textile World Dec. 1950
  - Item 3: 300 Years Old Stonington is Thirvinig Town, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: Don ross
    Notes: Aug. 24, 1949
  - Item 4: Advanced Management, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: American Velvet Co.
    Notes: Volume XVI March 1951
  - Item 5: Partners Share Profits, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: Reprinted from Partners Magazine Jan.-Feb. 1952
- Box: 1, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Directory of Products, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: AMF Incorporated
  - Item 2: AMF News, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 3: AMF News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Box: 1, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Employment Handbook, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Author: Amherst College
- Box: 1, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Your Group Hospital-Surgical-Medical and Extended Medical Benefits Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Author: Anaconda Company
    Notes: March 1, 1961
  - Item 2: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Notes: Jan.
- Box: 1, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Ideas in Action!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Author: Anaconda Wire and Cable Company
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 1
  - Item 2: Suggestions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Box: 1, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan Effective Oct. 1, 1963 for Salaried Empoyees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Author: Anchor Hocking Glass Corporation
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan Effective September 1, 1968 for Salaried Employees in Ohio, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 3: Education Assistance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 4: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: Amended as of Jan. 1, 1969
- Box: 1, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Anchorscope, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Notes: Vol.13, No. 2 July
  - Item 2: Management Information Communicator, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 2 Aug.
  - Item 3: Management Information Communication, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 1 Feb.
- Box: 1, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Our Suggestion System, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Author: Ansco (Gen'l Aniline and Film Corp.)
- Box: 1, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: A Plan for Your Retirement, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Author: Apex Electrical Manufacturing Co.
    Notes: June 1, 1951
- Box: 1, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: MOAC News, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Author: Appleton and Cox Corp.
    Notes: Vol. 7, No. 5
- Box: 1, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income for Employees of Arizona Public Service Company, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Author: Arizona Public Service Company
- Box: 1, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: For Thinkers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Author: Armco Steel Co.
  - Item 2: How to Prevent Back Injuries, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Box: 1, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Economics of Livestock and Meat, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Author: Armour Co.
    Notes: 7/1/53
  - Item 2: Armour Co. and the Meat Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 3: 77,000 People Own Armour Co., Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 4: Instructions for Handling the Armour Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 5: The Wage Chronology Series, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Notes: Series 4, No. 6
  - Item 6: Employees Representation Plan, 1922; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Notes: 3/30/22
  - Item 7: Progress Report Automation Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Author: Armour Co.:United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers AFL-CIO:Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL-CIO
  - Item 8: Progress Report Automation Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 9: Progress Report Automation Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 10: Progress Report Automation Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 11: The Armour Production Story, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 12: Armour Employees Representation Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Box: 1, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Extra Money Suggestion Program, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: Armstrong Cork Company
  - Item 2: Extra Money Suggestion Program, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 3: Decision, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: William N. Loucks
    Notes: Jan. 27 1964
  - Item 4: Arbitration, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: David B. Burger: Howard A. Goldberger
  - Item 5: Management's Right to Manage, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: Fred C. Edwards
  - Item 6: Arbitration, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: William J. Fellon
    Notes: March 28
  - Item 7: Arbitration, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: A. Howard Myers
    Notes: Jan. 20
  - Item 8: First Aid Training Leader's Guide, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Notes: Jan. 7
  - Item 9: The Importance of People, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 10: Suggestion Blank, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Box: 1, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Schwinn Employees Credit Union, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Author: Arnold Schwinn and Company
  - Item 2: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Box: 1, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Memorandum, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: Robert J. Koch
    Notes: May 10
  - Item 2: Blood Assurance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: The Arundel Corporation
  - Item 3: Plan for Salary Continuation During Disability (Sick Pay), 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Notes: 8/13/63
  - Item 4: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Notes: May 1
  - Item 5: Safety on the Streets, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 6: Group Life and Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: The Arundel Corporation:Arundel-Brooks Concrete Corporation
  - Item 7: Personal Procedures, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 8: Name Our Publication, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Notes: July-Aug.
  - Item 9: From the Ground Up, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Notes: Sept.-Oct.
  - Item 10: Required Physical Examinations Memorandum, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: M.G. Norris
    Notes: June 4
  - Item 11: Paid Vacations Memorandum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: C.W. Black
  - Item 12: Board of Directors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Author: Arundel Corporation
- Box: 1, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Regionalism in Asia, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Author: Arthur Paul
  - Item 2: University Cooperation and Asian Development Program, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Author: Asia Foundation
    Notes: Dec.
- Box: 1, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: As if the Future Mattered: Economic Policy in the New Administration, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Author: William D. Eberle: Richard N. Gardner
- Box: 1, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: The Contractor, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Author: Associated Builders and Contractors, Inc.
- Box: 1, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Time Tested Protection, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Author: Associated Hospital Service of N.Y.
- Box: 1, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: What it is What it Does, Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Author: Associated Industries of Cleveland
  - Item 2: Fall Industrial Relations Conference, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Notes: Oct. 8-9
- Box: 1, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Money for All!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Author: Associates Investment Company
- Box: 1, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Survey of Women Bank Officers, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Author: Association of Bank Women
- Box: 1, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Collective Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Author: Association of Dress Manufacturers, Inc.
- Box: 1, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Yes, Appearances DO Count!, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Author: Association Hospital Service of Philadelphia
- Box: 1, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Reporting Under the Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Author: Association of National Reporting Officers
  - Item 2: Handbook for Reporting Under the Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Item 3: Handbook for Reporting Under the Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Box: 1, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Highlights from Proposed Negotiations Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Author: Association of New Jersey State College Faculties, Inc.
  - Item 2: Highlights from Proposed Negotiations Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 3: Highlights from Proposed Negotiations Agreements, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Box: 1, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Atlanta University, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
    Author: Atlanta University
- Box: 1, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Author: Atlantic City Electric Company
- Box: 1, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Dixisteel In the Making, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Author: Atlantic Steel Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Atlas Employees' Suggestion Plan: Wanted, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Atlas Powder Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Let's Check, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: Auburn Chamber of Commerce
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: ABC's of Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Author: Auto Owners Insurance Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: You Ain't Seen Nothing Yet, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Frank Rising
    Notes: June 16
  - Item 2: Automotive Parts, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Automotive Parts Manufacturing Association
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employees Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Avco Lycoming Division
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: You and Lycoming, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Author: Avco Manufacturing Corp
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Pension Plan and Retirement Income and Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Awrey Bakeries, Inc.
  - Item 2: Retirement Income Plan for Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: March 1
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Money Talks, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Stanley A. Rasch
    Notes: April 14
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Author: Bache and Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing and Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Memorandum, 1964; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Harold L. Bache
  - Item 3: Your Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Bache and Co. 1966 Merit Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Depratment Store of Finance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: A. Charles Schwartz
    Notes: Reprinted Articles from The Christian Science Monitor
  - Item 2: A Wall Street Name for Over Eighty-Two Years, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Box: 2, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Bahrain, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Language: Engilsh: Arabic.
- Box: 2, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Contract, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Author: L.M. Relations Bakelite Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Enlisting Employee Support in an Emergency, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Employees Benefit Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: Ball Brothers
- Box: 2, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Author: Baltimore Gas and Electric Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Welcome, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Alfred Peevers
- Box: 2, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Safety Begins with Leadership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Author: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company
  - Item 2: Safety is Everybody's Job on the B&O, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Box: 2, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Information for the Employees of the Barbour Flax Spinning Company, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Author: Barbour Flax Spinning Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: MoneyFor Ideas! Barnes Family Suggestion System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Author: Barnes Manufacturing Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Personnel Procedures, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Author: Bassick Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Battelle News, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Author: Battelle Memorial Organization
- Box: 2, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of Pastry Shop Workers Union, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Author: Baur Pastry Shop
- Box: 2, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)